

# Alexey Li

### Junior Java developer/ Junior Full-stack developer

I have developed a deep interest in the field of IT over the years and I am currently undergoing Java developer training at INTEC in order to focus on software development as my area of expertise. Through this training, I have honed my skills in teamwork, problem-solving, time management, and maintaining a high level of resilience in stressful situations. I am driven by my proactive approach and an insatiable curiosity to learn, which constantly fuels my desire to enhance my efficiency on a daily basis.

## **Education**

Intec Brussel / Brussels, Belgium (NL) Java Enterprise Developer 2022 - 2023

ITlogia.ru E-learning IT (RU) Frontend development Bootcamp

2023 - 2023

Udemy.com / E-learning IT (EN) Java Bootcamp

**SpringBoot Bootcamp** 

2023 - 2023

IT-planet Academy (NL)

Devops engineer workshop 2023 - 2023

CVO Lethas & Semper / Brussels, Belgium (NL) **Dutch courses for non-native speakers** 

Beijing Insitute of Technology (BIT)/ Beijing, China (CN) **Economics and Management** 

Front-end

**Angular** 

**Bootstrap** 

Materialize

Version control /

management

Jira/Trello

Agile/Scrum

Git

UML

JavaScript / TypeScript

HTML

CSS

2011 - 2013

Kainar university / Almaty, Kazakshtan (RU/KZ) Finance, accounting, analysis and audit 2006 - 2011

## **Skills**

### Back-end / DATABASE

- Java 8/11
- · Spring (Boot, Cloud, Data, Security)
- JPA, Hibernate
- PostgreSQL, mySQL, Redis, **MongoDB**

#### **Testing frameworks / libraries**

- Junit 4/5
- Mockito
- Selenium
- Postman

#### **MOCKUP / WIREFRAMES**

- SmartDraw
- Adobe Photoshop
- Corel Draw

## Intec Brussel / Brussels, Belgium

Junior Java developer (Apprenticeship) Sept 2022 - present

Work Experience

- Designed and developed a universal WEB application for messaging API using Spring Boot + Security for the backend.

  MongoDB for the database, and Redis for connection
- management.

  Implemented Twillio for authentication, to ensure
- secure access to the application (2FA)
- Used Angular for front-end development.
  I performed automated testing with Selenium to ensure high code quality.
- **Swagger** for documentation.
- LINK backend
- Developed a concierge WEB application "My life" for managing work processes.
  Using Spring Boot for the backend.
  MySQL for the database and JPA-Hibernate for
- connection management with REST API
- **Swagger** for documentation.
- Used Angular for front-end development.
- I performed automated testing with
- LINK front-end LINK backend
- Developed a webshop WEB application "Vitrine".
- Using Spring Boot for the backend.
  PostgreSQL for the database and JPA-Hibernate for connection management with REST API
- Swagger for documentation.
- Used Angular for front-end development.
- I performed automated testing with LINK backend/front-end

# Carat Gold Almaty, Kazakhstan

Sales manager

Jun 2020 - Aug 2021

- Jewelry counseling
- Sales
- Valution

### **CNC** milling machine specialist Dunpo / Asan, South Korea Oct 2018 - Dec 2019

- Responsible for operation of CNC milling machine.
- Quality control of manufactured units.



# Alexey Li

Junior Java developer/ Junior Full-stack developer

I am currently available and looking for a new challenge in my career.

I am looking for backend/full-stack developer jobs, but I am also open to internships.

## **Contact Info**



alexey.li@mail.be



my CV porfolio



https://github.com/alekseylee



Alexey-Li



Brussels



+32-471-65-77-47



Driving license B

# Languages

- · Russian mother tongue
- · Kazakh mother tongue
- · English professional proficient
- Dutch upper-intermediate
- · Chineese pre-intermediate

## Interests & hobbies

- · Web design & development
- UI/UX
- Photography
- Gaming
- Twitch streaming

## **Work Experience**

## Deputy general manager Vitrine solutions / Almaty, Kazakhstan

May 2016 - Aug 2018

- Creating SRS (Software requirements specification) for project.

  I worked with design team for approving design for
- application.
  I worked with testers team for UX-UI design and
- functional testing for all application.

  I have involved 23 clients in the project, in the development phase (before project release)

## PR manager

business website "Kursiv.kz" / Almaty, Kazakhstan Dec 2014 - Apr 2016

- Sold website placements and developed advertising strategies for B2B clients.
  I have worked with such companies as Kcell, Allur Auto, Beeline, Samsung.

# **Entertaiment Department (Supervisor manager)**

Park resort "8ozer.kz" / Almaty, Kazakhstan Jul 2012 - Sept 2014

- HR management
- Customer service traning
- Accounting inventory

### For More Information



This barcode redirect to my personal

Website